<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support on YZKJ - Smart Home</title>
    <link>https://nembus.github.io/categories/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Support on YZKJ - Smart Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 08:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nembus.github.io/categories/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Use Policy</title>
      <link>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-use-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-use-policy/</guid>
      <description>1、Data usage limit  1.1、The use of data is limited to the business within the company, and the user group is limited to the authorized employees within the company.
 1.2、In the process of use, strictly follow the API development agreement of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s sales partner and use it appropriately.
 1.3、Keep up to date on Amazon policies that pertain to specific APIs (such as the Merchant Fulfillment API, Orders API, and Reports API) or functionality that your Application provides (such as Buyer-Seller messaging).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection Policy</title>
      <link>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-protection-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-protection-policy/</guid>
      <description>Through a certain data processing strategy to ensure that the data can be used reasonably and safely in the process of collection, verification, storage, access and use, the data processing strategy must include a complete data life cycle, and the strategy must include data collection, cleaning and management.
1、Security Requirements 1.1. Network Protection.  Implement network protection controls including network firewalls, network access control lists to deny access to unauthorized IP addrsses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Direct-to-Consumer Shipping And Tax Invoice , Tax Remittance &amp;&amp; About limitation of personal identity information and Incident response plan</title>
      <link>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-usage-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nembus.github.io/post/2021-10-26-data-usage-instructions/</guid>
      <description>1、about Direct-to-Consumer Shipping Our company has the use scenario of MFN, which needs to deliver goods directly to consumers. On the other hand, it is convenient for inventory allocation and management. The specific processes of shipment marking and logistics sending are as follows:
After confirming the delivery information of the order and the detailed information of the package, such as type, weight, size and delivery date, label and package the goods according to the distribution method and carrier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
